##### 

Decorative Interior Products

##### 

Construction Materials

##### 

Exterior Facades

##### 

Flooring and Wall Panels

##### [Kronodesign](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/decors/by_collection/kronodesign "Kronodesign")

##### [Kronoart](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/decors/by_collection/kronoart "Kronoart")

##### [Flooring and Wall Panels](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/products/kronoflooring " Flooring and Wall Panels ")

##### [Stock Availability](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/privacy/?action=index&controller=express_services&lang=0&action=index&controller=express_services "Stock Availability")

##### [Downloads](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/express-services/downloads)

##### [My Krono](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/my_krono)

##### Highlights

##### Events

##### Projects

[##### About Us](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/company/kronospan "About Us")Excellence in transforming wood

[##### Sustainability](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/company/sustainability "Sustainability")Sustainability

[##### News](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/company/news "News")Always be up to date

[##### Careers](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/company/careers "Careers")Kronospan Opportunities

There are no results.

##### Kronospan Trading SRL

Str. Mihail Kogalniceanu Nr.59  
Romania 515800 Sebes, Alba county

[

T +40 258 80 11 00](tel:+40 258 80 11 00)

T +40 258 80 11 00

[

F +40 258 80 11 99](tel:+40 258 80 11 99)

F +40 258 80 11 99

[

sales.sebes@kronospan.ro](mailto:sales.sebes@kronospan.ro)

View on map

×

Location and Language

International

en

Location and Language

Location

International Albania Algeria Andorra Argentina Armenia Australia Austria Bahrain Belarus Belgium Bolivia Bosnia and Herzegovina Brazil Bulgaria Canada Chile China Colombia Costa Rica Croatia Cyprus Czech Republic Denmark Dominican Republic Ecuador Egypt El Salvador Estonia Finland France Georgia Germany Ghana Greece Greenland Guadeloupe Guyana Hungary Iceland Ireland Italy Ivory Coast Kazakhstan Kuwait Kyrgyzstan Latvia Liechtenstein Lithuania Luxembourg Macedonia Malta Martinique Mexico Moldova Monaco Montenegro Netherlands Norway Oman Panama Paraguay Peru Poland Portugal Qatar Romania Russia San Marino Saudi Arabia Serbia Slovakia Slovenia Spain Sweden Switzerland Tajikistan Togo Trinidad and Tobago Turkey Turkmenistan UAE Ukraine United Kingdom Uruguay USA Uzbekistan Venezuela Yemen

Language

English

Contacts

##### Kronospan Trading SRL

Str. Mihail Kogalniceanu Nr.59  
Romania 515800 Sebes, Alba county

[

T +40 258 80 11 00](tel:+40 258 80 11 00)

T +40 258 80 11 00

[

F +40 258 80 11 99](tel:+40 258 80 11 99)

F +40 258 80 11 99

[

sales.sebes@kronospan.ro](mailto:sales.sebes@kronospan.ro)

View on map

×

##### [Organization](# "Organization")  

[##### About Us](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/company/kronospan "About Us")Excellence in transforming wood

[##### Sustainability](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/company/sustainability "Sustainability")Sustainability

[##### News](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/company/news "News")Always be up to date

[##### Careers](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/company/careers "Careers")Kronospan Opportunities

##### [Products](# "Products")  

##### 

Decorative Interior Products

##### 

Construction Materials

##### 

Exterior Facades

##### 

Flooring and Wall Panels

##### [Decors](# "Decors")  

##### [Kronodesign](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/decors/by_collection/kronodesign "Kronodesign")

##### [Kronoart](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/decors/by_collection/kronoart "Kronoart")

##### [Flooring and Wall Panels](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/products/kronoflooring " Flooring and Wall Panels ")

##### [Express Services](# "Express Services")  

##### [Downloads](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/privacy/?action=downloads&controller=express_services&type=downloads&lang=0&action=downloads&controller=express_services&type=downloads "Downloads")

##### [My Krono](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/my_krono "My Krono")

##### [Highlights](# "Highlights")  

##### [Highlights](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/highlights "Highlights")

##### [Events](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/my_krono/krono_events "Events")

##### [Projects](https://www.kronospan-worldwide.com/en_EN/projects "Projects")

PAGE

NOT FOUND

We are sorry, the page you're looking for could not be found.

It may not longer exist or may have been moved.

This website uses functional cookies and anonymous tracking technologies to assist with navigation and improve our marketing services. Please accept or refuse the saving of functional cookies by selecting one of the options. For more information, please read our [Privacy policy](http://kronospan-express.com/terms_and_conditions/files/Privacy-policy-KRONOSPAN-EXPRESS-EN.pdf "Privacy policy")

© Kronoplus Limited 2024

##### ##### Subscribe to our newsletter  

Sign up now to be the first to get notified of upcoming events, corporate news, new products and design trends.  
  
I acknowledge and agree to Kronospan’s [**Terms and Conditions**](https://kronospan.com/terms_and_conditions/files/Terms-Conditions-202304.pdf "Terms and Conditions") and [**Privacy Policy**](https://kronospan.com/terms_and_conditions/files/Privacy-policy-KRONOSPAN_COM-EN.pdf "Kronospan's Privacy Policy") and to Kronospan's use of my contact information to communicate with me about its products, services or events.

Country Albania Algeria Andorra Argentina Armenia Australia Austria Bahrain Belarus Belgium Bolivia Bosnia and Herzegovina Brazil Bulgaria Cameroon Canada Chile China Colombia Congo Costa Rica Croatia Cyprus Czech Republic Denmark Dominican Republic Ecuador Egypt El Salvador Estonia Fiji Finland France Gabon Georgia Germany Ghana Greece Greenland Guadeloupe Guinea Guyana Hong Kong Hungary Iceland India Indonesia Iran Ireland Israel Italy Japan Jordan Kazakhstan Kenya Kosovo Kuwait Kyrgyzstan Latvia Lebanon Libya Lichtenstein Lithuania Luxembourg Macau Macedonia Madagascar Malaysia Malta Martinique Mauritius Mexico Moldova Monaco Montenegro Morocco Netherlands New Caledonia New Zealand Nigeria Norway Oman Pakistan Panama Papua New Guinea Paraguay Peru Philippines Poland Portugal Qatar Reunion Island Romania Russia San Marino Saudi Arabia Senegal Serbia Seychelles Singapore Slovakia Slovenia Spain Sweden Switzerland Turkey UAE Ukraine United Kingdom USA Yemen

##### Organization  

##### Privacy & Legal  

##### Support & Advice  

##### News  

##### Subscribe to our newsletter

Sign up now to be the first to get notified of upcoming events, corporate news, new products and design trends.  
  
I acknowledge and agree to Kronospan’s [**Terms and Conditions**](https://kronospan.com/terms_and_conditions/files/Terms-Conditions-202304.pdf "Terms and Conditions") and [**Privacy Policy**](https://kronospan.com/terms_and_conditions/files/Privacy-policy-KRONOSPAN_COM-EN.pdf "Kronospan's Privacy Policy") and to Kronospan's use of my contact information to communicate with me about its products, services or events.

Country \* Albania Algeria Andorra Argentina Armenia Australia Austria Bahrain Belarus Belgium Bolivia Bosnia and Herzegovina Brazil Bulgaria Cameroon Canada Chile China Colombia Congo Costa Rica Croatia Cyprus Czech Republic Denmark Dominican Republic Ecuador Egypt El Salvador Estonia Fiji Finland France Gabon Georgia Germany Ghana Greece Greenland Guadeloupe Guinea Guyana Hong Kong Hungary Iceland India Indonesia Iran Ireland Israel Italy Japan Jordan Kazakhstan Kenya Kosovo Kuwait Kyrgyzstan Latvia Lebanon Libya Lichtenstein Lithuania Luxembourg Macau Macedonia Madagascar Malaysia Malta Martinique Mauritius Mexico Moldova Monaco Montenegro Morocco Netherlands New Caledonia New Zealand Nigeria Norway Oman Pakistan Panama Papua New Guinea Paraguay Peru Philippines Poland Portugal Qatar Reunion Island Romania Russia San Marino Saudi Arabia Senegal Serbia Seychelles Singapore Slovakia Slovenia Spain Sweden Switzerland Turkey UAE Ukraine United Kingdom USA Yemen

##### [Organization](https://kronospan.com/en_EN/company "Organization")

##### [Privacy & Legal](javascript:; "Privacy & Legal")

##### [Support & Advice](javascript:; "Support & Advice")

##### [News](https://kronospan.com/en_EN/company/news "News")

© Kronoplus Limited 2024

×
